Guide to the John Canemaker Animation Collection MSS.040
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Book Collection, 1945-2012; 3 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons
  - [unidentified], undated (Box 94, Folder 20)
- Series IV: Periodical Collection, 40916
  Scope and Contents note
  These items are housed in the Fales Library. A list of the periodicals is available in the Reading Room.
- Series V: Audio & Video Tape Collection., 40697
  Both the audio and videotape materials were originally housed in the Avery Fisher Center for Music and Media. In 2003, the audiotapes were transferred to the Fales Library and Special Collections. The videotapes remain in the Avery Fisher Center. Following is a list of the audiotapes.
  - Subseries A: Audio Interviews, 40714
    - J.R. Bray interview by John Canemaker; Bridgeport, Connecticut, March 25, 1974; ID: 040.0001; 40814 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0001, Case 040.0001)
      Existence and Location of Copies
      Access CD available.
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
      Original Format: Audiocassette, TDK C-60
      Duration: 57 minutes
    - Art Babbitt remembers Bill Tytla in Los Angeles, March 1975; ID: 040.0002; 40813 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0002, Case 040.0002)
      Duration: 54 minutes.
    - Art Babbitt interview by John Canemaker, New York City, June 4, 1975; ID: 040.0003; 40812 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0003, Case 040.0003)
      Duration: 63 minutes.
    - Art Babbitt interview by John Canemaker, New York City., 1975; ID: 040.0004; 40811 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0004, Case 040.0004)
    - Side A: Ollie Johnston and Les Clark interviews, Disney Studio, Burbank, California; Side B: Frank Thomas, Disney Studio, July 5, 1973/ July 6, 1973; ID: 040.0005; 40810 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0005, Case 040.0005)
      Original Format: Audiocassette, TDK C-60SD
    - Otto Messmer, Fort Lee, New Jersey, March 5, 1975; ID: 040.0006; 40809 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0006, Case 040.0006)
      Duration: 64 minutes.
    - John A Fitzsimmons (Winsor McCay's assistant), Rockville Center, New York City, September 22, 1974; ID: 040.0007; 40808 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0007, Case 040.0007)
    - Side A: Otto Messmer; Side B: George Bakes on Bill Tytla, New York City, March 5, 1975/March 11, 1975; ID: 040.0008; 40807 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0008, Case 040.0008)
    - Shamus Culhane, New York City, February 13, 1974; ID: 040.0009; 40806 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0009, Case 040.0009)
    - Shamus Culhane, New York City, February 13, 1974; ID: 040.0010; 40805 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0010, Case 040.0010)
      Duration: 38 minutes.
    - Terri Gilliam (backstage City Center Theater), New York City, April 30, 1976; ID: 040.0011; 40804 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0011, Case 040.0011)
      Duration: 29 minutes.
    - Emery Hawkins, New York City, January 12, 1976; ID: 040.0012; 40803 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0012, Case 040.0012)
      Original Format: Audiocassette, TDK Maverick M C60
    - Otto Messmer (final interview, talks about early life, etc.), January 29, 1979; ID: 040.0013; 40802 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0013, Case 040.0013)
      Original Format: Audiocassette, Scotch C-60
    - Tex Hensen "remembers Walt Disney and Studio". Recorded in Dallas, 1978; ID: 040.0014; 40801 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0014, Case 040.0014)
      Original Format: Audiocassette, Irish Series 2000-60
      Duration: 61 minutes.
    - Bruno Bozzetto, New York City, February 12, 1979.; ID: 040.0015; 40800 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0015, Case 040.0015)
      Original Format: Audiocassette, Ampex Plus Series-60
    - George Dunning, Ottowa, Canada, Sept. 1, 1978; ID: 040.0016; 40799 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0016, Case 040.0016)
      Original Format: Audiocassette, Ampex 361-C60
      Duration: 47 minutes.
    - Side A: Don Duckwall; Side B: Eric Larson, Heidi Guedel, Emily Guliano, Walt Disney Studio, Burbank, California, April 25, 1978; ID: 040.0017; 40798 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0017, Case 040.0017)
      Original Format: Audiocassette, Recoton-ultra flow, 60
      Duration: 60 minutes.
    - Len Lye, New York City, interviewed by Joseph Kennedy and John Canemaker, August 22, 1976; ID: 040.0018; 40797 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0018, Case 040.0018_pt.1, Case 040.0018_pt.2)
      Access CDs available. Please request parts 1 and 2.
      Original Format: Audiocassette, Scotch C-90
      Duration: 92 minutes.
    - Side A: Len Lye, New York City; Side B: Walter Lantz, June 16, 1977; ID: 040.0019; 40796 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0019, Case 040.0019)
      Original Format: Audiocassette, TDK C-90
    - Side A: Confessions of a Star Dreamer audio mix; Side B: Walter Lanz, June 16, 1977; ID: 040.0020; 40795 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0020, Case 040.0020)
      Original Format: Audiocassette, Sony C-60
      Duration: 41 minutes.
    - Richard Williams, New York City, July 18, 1976; ID: 040.0021; 40794 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0021, Case 040.0021_pt.1, Case 040.0021_pt.2)
      Duration: 93 minutes.
    - Side A: Richard Williams, New York City; Side B: Joe Raposo (on Raggedy Ann and Andy), July 19, 1976; ID: 040.0022; 40793 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0022, Case 040.0022_pt.1, Case 040.0022_pt.2)
      Duration: 84 minutes.
    - Side A: David R. Smith, Disney Archives, Burbank, California; Disney animation trainees; Side B: Ward Kimball, Arcadia, California, July 6, 1973/July 7, 1973; ID: 040.0023; 40792 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0023, Case 040.0023)
    - Ward Kimball, Arcadia, California, July 7, 1973; ID: 040.0024; 40791 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0024, Case 040.0024)
    - Harold Walker on Pat Sullivan, Otto Messmer, and Felix the Cat, 1978; ID: 040.0025; 40790 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0025, Case 040.0025_pt.1, Case 040.0025_pt.2)
      Original Format: Audiocassette, Intermagnetics-90
      Duration: 90 minutes.
    - Art Babbitt on Don Graham and Disney art school, February 21, 1979; ID: 040.0026; 40789 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0026, Case 040.0026)
      Original Format: Audiocassette, Racal-Zonal C-90
      Duration: 40 minutes.
    - Frank Thomas answers list of questions., September 9, 1974; ID: 040.0027; 40788 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0027, Case 040.0027)
      Duration: 44 minutes.
    - Grim Natwick, New York City, May 19, 1974; ID: 040.0028; 40787 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0028, Case 040.0028)
    - Richard Williams on Raggedy Ann and Andy, New York City, December 2, 1975; ID: 040.0029; 40786 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0029, Case 040.0029)
      Duration: 58 minutes.Access CDs available. Please request parts 1 and 2.
    - Elfriede Fischinger and William Moritz interviewed by P. Adams Sitney on ArtForum, May 6, 1977; ID: 040.0030; 40785 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0030, Case 040.0030)
      Original Format: Audiocassette, Memorex MRX2 Oxide, 60
      Duration: 55 minutes.Access CDs available. Please request parts 1 and 2.
    - George Griffin, New York City, September 5, 1985; ID: 040.0031; 40784 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0031, Case 040.0031)
      Original Format: Audiocassette, Maxell XLII 60
    - Lou Bunin, New York City, June 3, 1986.; ID: 040.0032; 40783 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0032, Case 040.0032_pt.1, Case 040.0032_pt.2)
      Original Format: Audiocassette, Maxell XLII 90
      Duration: 95 minutes.
    - Lou Bunin, New York City, June 17, 1986; ID: 040.0033; 40782 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0033, Case 040.0033)
      Duration: 19 minutes.
    - Douglas Trumbull, Midwest Film Conference, Chicago, 1981; ID: 040.0034; 40781 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0034, Case 040.0034_pt.1, Case 040.0034_pt.2)
      Duration: 87 minutes.
    - Gary Kurtz ( Star Wars Press Conference), May 24, 1977; ID: 040.0035; 40780 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0035, Case 040.0035)
      Duration: 55 minutes.
    - Chuck Jones, guest on Dick Cavette television program, October 25, 1979; ID: 040.0036; 40779 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0036, Case 040.0036)
      Duration: 53 minutes.
    - Willis Pyle, May 16, 1973; ID: 040.0037; 40778 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0037, Case 040.0037)
      Duration: 58 minutes.
    - June Foray, New York City, October 14, 1975; ID: 040.0038; 40777 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0038, Case 040.0038)
      Duration: 62 minutes.
    - David Hilberman, Santa Cruz, California, June 16, 1979; ID: 040.0039; 40776 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0039, Case 040.0039)
    - David Hilberman, Santa Cruz, California, June 16, 1979; ID: 040.0040; 40775 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0040, Case 040.0040)
    - Jules Engel, July 1, 1975; ID: 040.0041; 40774 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0041, Case 040.0041)
    - Peter Ellenshaw, lunch at Disney Studio, with Frank Thomas, Ollie Johnston, Joseph Kennedy, Chuck Richardson (Disney Public Relations), June 19, 1979; ID: 040.0042; 40773 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0042, Case 040.0042)
    - Side A: Stanley Sills, ITT, New York City; Side B: Elfriede Fischinger., October 25, 1976/May 6, 1977; ID: 040.0043; 40772 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0043, Case 040.0043)
      Duration: 71 minutes.
    - John Canemaker reading from John Fitzsimmons' remembrances of Winsor McCay., undated; ID: 040.0044; 40771 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0044, Case 040.0044)
      Original Format: Audiocassette, Sony UX 60
      Duration: 39 minutes.
    - Al Rezek and Tissa David, August 8, 1976; ID: 040.0045; 40770 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0045, Case 040.0045_pt.1, Case 040.0045_pt.2)
    - Pat Thackery; Tissa David, July 21, 1976/August 8, 1976; ID: 040.0046; 40769 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0046, Case 040.0046_pt.1, Case 040.0046_pt.2)
    - R.O. Blechman, New York City, July 14, 1978; ID: 040.0047; 40768 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0047, Case 040.0047)
      Duration: 20 minutes.
    - Side A: Michael Sisson, Mike Sporn; Side B: Richard Williams, July 15, 1976/July 18, 1976; ID: 040.0048; 40767 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0048, Case 040.0048_pt.1, Case 040.0048_pt.2)
    - Susan Pitt, March 16, 1979; ID: 040.0049; 40766 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0049, Case 040.0049_pt.1, Case 040.0049_pt.2)
      Duration: 83 minutes.
    - Mr. and Mrs. Otto Messmer (part of final interview), January 29, 1979; ID: 040.0050; 40765 (Box V.3, Media ID: 040.0050, Case 040.0050)
      Original Format: Audiocassette, Maxell UR 60
      Duration: 31 minutes.
    - Al Eugster, May 12, 1976; ID: 040.0051; 40764 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0051, Case 040.0051)
    - George Bakes on Bill Tytla, 1975; ID: 040.0052; 40763 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0052, Case 040.0052)
    - Adrienne Tytla (Bill Tytla's wife), Old Lyme, Connecticut, April 11, 1975; ID: 040.0053; 40762 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0053, Case 040.0053)
    - Adrienne Tytla, April 11, 1975; ID: 040.0054; 40761 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0054, Case 040.0054)
    - George Griffin, November 6, 1974; ID: 040.0055; 40760 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0055, Case 040.0055)
    - Paul Bray, Jr. (J.R. Bray's grandson), April 19, 1974; ID: 040.0056; 40759 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0056, Case 040.0056)
    - Milt Kahl at School of Visual Arts, with John Culhane, May 24, 1973; ID: 040.0057; 40758 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0057, Case 040.0057)
    - Milt Kahl at School of Visual Arts, 1973; ID: 040.0058; 40757 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0058, Case 040.0058)
    - Ron Husband, Lorna Pomeroy, Dan Hansen, Jim Coleman, Pete Young, Steve Hulett, Dan Haskett, Jerry Rees, Bill Croyer, et al., Disney Studio, Burbank, California, April 25, 1978; ID: 040.0059; 40756 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0059, Case 040.0059)
    - Side A: Disney Seminar at Lincoln Center (Film Society) with John Culhane, Frank Thomas, Ken Anderson, Woolie Reitherman, and Ken Anderson on character design and development; Side B: Frank Thomas on animation techniques., June 18, 1973; ID: 040.0060; 40755 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0060, Case 040.0060)
    - Side A: Disney Seminar at Lincoln Center (Film Society) with Frank Thomas, Ken Anderson, and Woolie Reitherman; Side B: screening of television program The Plausible Impossible, July 19, 1973; ID: 040.0061; 40754 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0061, Case 040.0061)
    - Frank Thomas on optical effects, July 19, 1973; ID: 040.0062; 40753 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0062, Case 040.0062)
    - Disney seminar on trainee program in animation., July 20, 1973; ID: 040.0063; 40752 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0063, Case 040.0063)
    - Zack Schwartz, New York City, September 12, 1979; ID: 040.0064; 40751 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0064, Case 040.0064)
    - Zack Schwartz, New York City, September 12, 1979; ID: 040.0065; 40750 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0065, Case 040.0065)
    - Zack Schwartz, September 18, 1979; ID: 040.0066; 40749 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0066, Case 040.0066)
    - Zack Schwartz, September 18, 1979; ID: 040.0067; 40748 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0067, Case 040.0067)
    - Fred Stuthman, Richard Horner, and Cozmo Anzillotti, interviewed as part of research for John Canemaker's 1977 book, The Animated Raggedy Ann and Andy, July 6-9, 1976; ID: 040.0068; 40747 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0068, Case 040.0068)
    - Jim Logan, Eric Goldberg, George Bakes, Cosmo Pepe, and Harry Chang, interviewed as part of research for John Canemaker's 1977 book, The Animated Raggedy Ann and Andy, July 9-12, 1976; ID: 040.0069; 40746 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0069, Case 040.0069)
    - Harry Chang, continued; Carol Millican, Dan Haskett, and Ida Greenberg, interviewed as part of research for John Canemaker's 1977 book, The Animated Raggedy Ann and Andy, July 12-13, 1976; ID: 040.0070; 40745 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0070, Case 040.0070)
    - Ida Greenberg, continued; Sue Butterworth, and Michael Sisson, interviewed as part of research for John Canemaker's 1977 book, The Animated Raggedy Ann and Andy, July 13-15, 1976; ID: 040.0071; 40744 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0071, Case 040.0071)
    - Hollywood Raggedy Ann studio; Hal Ambro, John Kimball and Corny Cole, interviewed as part of research for John Canemaker's 1977 book, The Animated Raggedy Ann and Andy, July 26, 1976.; ID: 040.0072; 40743 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0072, Case 040.0072_pt.1, Case 040.0072_pt.2)
      Access CD available. Please request parts 1 and 2
    - John Kimball, continued; Grim Natwick, and Art Babbitt, interviewed as part of research for John Canemaker's 1977 book, The Animated Raggedy Ann and Andy, July 27, 1976; ID: 040.0073; 40742 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0073, Case 040.0073_pt.1, Case 040.0073_pt.2)
      Access CD available. Please request parts 1 and 2.
    - John Halas, London, November 5, 1979; ID: 040.0074; 40741 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0074, Case 040.0074)
    - William Pomerance (on the Disney 1941 strike), April 17, 1979; ID: 040.0075; 40740 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0075, Case 040.0075)
    - Joe Oriolo (on Felix the Cat), May 21, 1975; ID: 040.0076; 40739 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0076, Case 040.0076)
      Duration: 24 minutes
    - Joe Hambrook (on George Dunning and the BBC), November 25, 1979; ID: 040.0077; 40738 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0077, Case 040.0077)
      Duration: 62 minutes
    - Richard Williams on George Dunning, November 20, 1979; ID: 040.0078; 40737 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0078, Case 040.0078)
      Duration: 31 minutes
    - Art Babbitt, New York City, July 12, 1979; ID: 040.0079; 40736 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0079, Case 040.0079)
      Duration: 61 minutes
    - Art Babbitt, New York City, July 12, 1979; ID: 040.0080; 40735 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0080, Case 040.0080)
      Duration: 26 minutes.
    - Douglas Leigh on Otto Messmer and electric sign work, April 19, 1984; ID: 040.0081; 40734 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0081, Case 040.0081)
      Duration: 32 minutes
    - Disney Studios: Art Stevens, Mel Shaw, Ed Hansen (on The Fox and Hound, April 16, 1981; ID: 040.0082; 40733 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0082, Case 040.0082)
      Duration: 49 minutes
    - Frank Thomas and Ollie Johnston, interview by Patricia McCann on WOR Radio, New York City, October 7, 1981; ID: 040.0083; 40732 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0083, Case 040.0083)
    - John Halas and Joy Batchelor en route to Cambridge, England, November 9, 1979; ID: 040.0084; 40731 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0084, Case 040.0084)
      Duration: 65 minutes
    - Sally Cruikshank, June 11, 1981; ID: 040.0085; 40730 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0085, Case 040.0085)
    - Sally Cruikshank (on Ruthless People titles; interview with Ted Wollery, August 7, 1986; ID: 040.0086; 40729 (Media V.A.4, Media ID: 040.0086, Case 040.0086)
      Duration: 29 minutes
      Original Format: Audiocassette, Maxell C60
    - Independent Animators Interviews, conducted by Kit Laybourne for grant project [1979], including G. Griffin, Caroline Leaf, and John Canemaker., ID: 040.0087; 40728 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0087, Case 040.0087)
      Duration: 81 minutes
    - Independent Animators Interviews: G. Griffin, Caroline Leaf, Mary Beams, Co Hoedeman Eli Noyes and John Canemaker, 1979; ID: 040.0088; 40727 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0088, Case 040.0088)
      Duration: 79 minutes
    - David Tissa; George Dunning recorded from CBS Camera Three, May 29, 1973/May 30, 1973; ID: 040.0089; 40726 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0089, Folder 40.0189)
      Duration: 63 minutes
    - John Canemaker interviewed by Radio Smithsonian, Washington, D.C., 1979; ID: 040.0090; 40725 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0090, Case 040.0090)
      Duration: 30 minutes
    - Fred Berner: final days of Raggedy Ann and Andy, August 23, 1977; ID: 040.0091; 40724 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0091, Case 040.0091)
    - Fred Berner: final days of Raggedy Ann and Andy, August 26, 1977; ID: 040.0092; 40723 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0092, Case 040.0092)
    - Frank Thomas and Ollie Johnston, interviewed by John Canemaker at the Midwest Film Conference, Chicago., 1981; ID: 040.0093; 40722 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0093, Case 040.0093 pt.1, Case 040.0093 pt.2)
      Duration: 91 minutes
    - Thomas and Johnston, Midwest Film Conference, 1981; ID: 040.0094; 40721 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0094, Case 040.0094)
    - John Canemaker lecture on early animation, Midwest Film Conference, 1981; ID: 040.0095; 40720 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0095, Case 040.0095)
      Duration: 58 minutes
    - Rudy Zamora, at Hanna-Barbera Studios, Los Angeles, June 21, 1979; ID: 040.0096; 40719 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0096, Case 040.0096)
    - Bob Clampett interviewed by John Canemaker at the Midwest Film Conference, February 13, 1982; ID: 040.0097; 40718 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0097, Case 040.0097)
      Duration: 72 minutes
    - Lecture by John Canemaker on early animators at the "Pioneers" -- LA Film Exposition, 1978; ID: 040.0098; 40717 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0098, Case 040.0098 pt.1, Case 040.0098 pt.2)
      Duration: 87 minutes
    - Interviews by John Canemaker of a panel of early animators, including Grim Natwick, Walter Lantz, Rudy Isling, Richard Huemer, and Harry Love at the "History Makers" -- LA Film Exposition, 1978; ID: 040.0099; 40716 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0099, Case 040.0099)
      Duration: 70 minutes
    - Art Babbitt, recorded letter to John Canemaker, May 26, 1979; ID: 040.0100; 40715 (Box V.4, Media ID: 040.0100, Case 040.0100)
- Oversize: Series I: Documentary Material, 40689
  - Subseries B: People, 40690
    - Disney, Walt: FANTASIA, SONG OF THE SOUTH, SUMMER MAGIC, undated; 40696 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Kinney, Jack: Galleys of "Walt Disney & Other Assorted Characters", undated; 40695 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Disney, Walt: AnimationArt Calendar, 1985; 40694 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Disney, Walt: FANTASIA, undated; 40693 (Box 29, Folder 1-2)
    - Jones, Chuck - Artwork, undated; 40692 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Canemaker, John: Books: Tex Avery, undated; 40691 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Cruikshank, Sally: Quasi At the Quackadero & Suspended Animation Exhibit Poster, [1981]; 261661 (Folder 4 Left)
- Oversize: Series II: Graphic Material, 40670
  - Subseries A: Animators' Artwork, 40931
    Unless otherwise noted, Series II-A are in oversize boxes
    - Babbitt, Art, undated; 40981 (Box II.A.01, Folder 1)
    - Canemaker, John - Films - BOTTOM'S DREAM, undated; 40980 (Box II.A.01, Folder 2)
    - Canemaker,John - Films - CHILDREN'S TELEVISION WORKSHOP-DNA CONCERTO, undated; 40979 (Box II.A.01, Folder 3)
    - Canemaker: CHILDREN'S TELEVISIONWORKSHOP-SHAPE OF MATH, undated; 40978 (Box II.A.01, Folder 4)
    - Canemaker,John: CONFESSIONS OF A STARDREAMER, undated; 40977 (Box II.A.01, Folder 5)
    - Canemaker, John: COUNT ON KOTEX commercial, undated; 40975 (Box II.A.2, Folder 6)
    - Canemaker, John: THE 40'S, undated; 40974 (Box II.A.2, Folder 7)
    - Canemaker, John: GREED, undated; 40973 (Box II.A.2, Folder 8)
    - Canemaker, John: THE HUNGER PROJECT, undated; 40972 (Box II.A.2, Folder 9)
    - Canemaker, John: JOHN LENNON SKETCHBOOK, undated; 40971 (Box II.A.2, Folder 10)
    - Canemaker, John: LATE FOR DINNER, undated; 40970 (Box II.A.3, Folder 11)
    - Canemaker, John: LAUGHTER IS GOOD MEDICINE, undated; 40969 (Box II.A.3, Folder 12)
    - Canemaker, John: NEMO DREAMSEQUENCE, undated; 40968 (Box II.A.3, Folder 13)
    - Canemaker, John: RISINGSTAR VIDEO logo, undated; 40967 (Box II.A.3, Folder 14)
    - Canemaker, John: SEARCHING CA, OR KAZ VS. THEGYPSY MOTH, undated; 40966 (Box II.A.3, Folder 15)
    - Canemaker, John: SILVER SCREEN PARTNERS IV, undated; 40965 (Box II.A.3, Folder 16)
    - Canemaker, John-Films-STREET FREAKS, undated; 40964 (Box II.A.4, Folder 17)
    - Canemaker, John: WHAT DOCHILDREN THINK WHENTHEY THINK OF THE BOMB?, undated; 40963 (Box II.A.4, Folder 18)
    - Canemaker, John: WHO'S THAT GIRL?, undated; 40962 (Box II.A.4, Folder 19)
    - Canemaker, John: THE WIZARD'S SON, undated; 40961 (Box II.A.4, Folder 20)
    - Canemaker, John: THE WIZARD'S SON, undated; 40960 (Folder 2 Left)
    - Canemaker, John: THE WORLD ACCORDING TOGARP, undated; 40959 (Box II.A.5, Folder 21)
    - Canemaker, John: THE WORLD ACCORDING TO GARP, undated; 40958 (Folder 3 Left)
    - Canemaker, John: YOU DON"T HAVE TO DIE/ SELF PORTRAIT-H.B.O. [1 of 2], 1988; 261669 (Folder 6 Right)
    - Canemaker, John: YOU DON"T HAVE TO DIE/ SELF PORTRAIT- H.B.O. [2 of 2], 1988; 261670 (Folder 7 Right)
    - Canemaker,John: Miscellaneous, undated; 40957 (Box II.A.5, Folder 22)
    - David, Tissa, undated; 40956 (Box II.A.5, Folder 23)
    - David, Tissa-Films-RAGGEDY ANN & ANDY ***see*** Williams, Richard, undated; 40955
    - Disney,Walt-Books-Treasures OF Disney Animation, undated; 40954 (Box II.A.6, Folder 24)
    - Disney, Walt-Films-DON QUIXOTE, undated; 40953 (Box II.A.6, Folder 25)
    - Disney,Walt-Films-JOHNNY APPLESEED, undated; 40952 (Box II.A.6, Folder 26)
    - Disney,Walt-Films-MAKE MINE MUSIC, undated; 40951 (Box II.A.6, Folder 27)
    - Disney,Walt-Films-MELODY TIME-BUMBLE BOOGIEsequence, undated; 40950 (Box II.A.6, Folder 28)
    - Disney, Walt-Films-ONCE UPON A WINTERTIM Esequence, undated; 40949 (Box II.A.6, Folder 29)
    - Disney, Walt-Films-PETER PAN, undated; 40948 (Box II.A.6, Folder 30)
    - Disney,Walt-Films-PINOCCHIO with other films, photostat mock-ups, undated; 40947 (Folder 9)
    - Disney,Walt-Films-SNOW WHITE & THE SEVENDWARFS, undated; 40946 (Box II.A.6, Folder 31)
    - Disney, Walt-Films-30 20" x 40" photostat mock-ups [1 of 2], undated; 40945 (Folder 11)
    - Disney, Walt-Films-30 20" x 40" photostat mock-ups [2 of 2], [undated]; 261641 (Folder 10)
    - Disney, Walt: Miscellaneous, undated; 40944 (Box II.A.6, Folder 32)
    - Dunbar, Geoff-Films-UBU, undated; 40943 (Box II.A.7, Folder 33)
    - Fischinger, Oskar, undated; 40942 (Box II.A.7, Folder 34)
    - Fleischer, Max &Dave, undated; 40941 (Box II.A.7, Folder 35)
    - Freleng, Friz, undated; 40940 (Box II.A.7, Folder 36)
    - Jones, Chuck, undated; 40939 (Box II.A.7, Folder 37)
    - Klein, I., undated; 40938 (Box II.A.7, Folder 38)
    - Petty, Sara, undated; 40937 (Box II.A.8, Folder 39)
    - Ring, Borge, undated; 40936 (Box II.A.8, Folder 40)
    - Sporn,Michael, undated; 40935 (Box II.A.8, Folder 41)
    - Thomas, Frank & Johnston, Ollie:'-Books-Too Funny FOR Words, undated; 40934 (Box II.A.8, Folder 42)
    - Tytla,William, undated; 40933 (Box II.A.8, Folder 43)